{
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "What is H2O2 commonly known as?",
      "choices" : ["Water", "Hydrogen peroxide","Salt"],
      "rightanswer": "Hydrogen peroxide"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "Which of the following elements is not a liquid around room temperature?",
      "choices" : [" Magnesium", "Bromine","Mercury"],
      "rightanswer": "Magnesium"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "Which of the followings does not contain potassium?",
      "choices" : ["Soap", "Gunpowder","Bread"],
      "rightanswer": "Bread"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "What do we call the process in which an atomâ€™s nucleus splits into smaller elements?",
      "choices" : ["Nuclear fusion", "Nuclear fission","Nuclear reaction"],
      "rightanswer": "Nuclear fission"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "What is the role of salt in a saline solution or a solution of saltwater?",
      "choices" : ["Sol", "Solvent","Solute"],
      "rightanswer": "Solute"
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "Which of the followings is not a rare-earth element?",
      "choices" : ["Terbium", "Gold","Lanthanum"],
      "rightanswer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "If we fill a glass with ice cubes and water. What will occur when the ice melts?",
      "choices" : [" The water level remains the same", "The water level increases slightly","The water level decreases slightly"],
      "rightanswer": "The water level decreases slightly"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "Based on the pH level, how can we describe milk?",
      "choices" : ["Slightly acidic", "Neutral","Slightly basic"],
      "rightanswer": " Slightly acidic"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "Which of the following elements is heavier than iron?",
      "choices" : ["Gold", "Manganese","Potassium"],
      "rightanswer": "Gold"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": " What does AMU stand for in chemistry?",
      "choices" : ["Atomic Matter Unit", " Atomic Mass Unit","Accelerated Mass Unit"],
      "rightanswer": "Atomic Mass Unit"
    }
  ]
}